U.S. Manpower Administration "Manpower Daily Reporter" Newsletters 5380
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- April, 1969; Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Item 13: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday April 10, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday April 9, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday April 8, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday April 7, 1969. Item is in English.
- May, 1969; Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday May 29, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday May 27, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday May 26, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Copy 2. Monday May 26, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday May 23, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday May 22, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday May 21, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday May 20, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday May 19, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday May 15, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday May 14, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday May 13, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday May 12, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday May 9, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday May 8, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday May 6, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday May 5, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday May 2, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday May 1, 1969. Item is in English.
- June, 1969; Publication (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 18)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday June 30, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 18)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday June 27, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 18)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday June 26, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 18)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday June 25, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 18)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday June 24, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 18)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday June 23, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 18)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday June 20, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 18)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday June 19, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 18)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday June 17, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 18)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday June 16, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 18)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday June 13, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 18)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday June 12, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 18)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday June 11, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 18)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday June 10, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 18)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday June 9, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 18)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday June 6, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 18)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday June 5, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 18)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday June 4, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 18)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday June 3, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 18)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday June 2, 1969. Item is in English.
- July, 1969; Publication (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 19)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday July 31, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 19)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday July 30, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 19)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday July 29, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 19)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday July 28, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 19)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday July 25, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 19)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday July 24, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 19)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday July 23, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 19)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday July 22, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 19)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday July 18, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 19)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday July 17, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 19)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday July 16, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 19)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday July 15, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 19)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday July 14, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 19)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday July 11, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 19)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday July 10, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 19)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday July 9, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 19)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday July 8, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 19)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday July 7, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 19)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday July 4, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 19)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday July 3, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 19)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday July 2, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 19)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday July 1, 1969. Item is in English.
- August, 1969; Publication (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 20)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday August 29, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 20)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday August 28, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 20)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday August 27, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 20)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday August 26, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 20)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday August 25, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 20)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday August 22, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 20)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday August 21, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 20)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday August 20, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 20)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday August 19, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 20)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday August 18, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 20)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday August 15, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 20)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday August 14, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 20)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday August 13, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 20)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday August 12, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 20)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday August 8, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 20)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday August 7, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 20)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday August 6, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 20)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday August 5, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 20)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday August 1, 1969. Item is in English.
- September, 1969; Publication (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 21)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday September 30, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 21)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday September 29, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 21)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday September 26, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 21)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday September 25, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 21)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday September 24, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 21)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday September 23, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 21)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday September 22, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 21)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday September 19, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 21)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday September 18, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 21)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday September 17, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 21)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday September 16, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 21)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday September 15, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 21)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday September 11, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 21)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday September 10, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 21)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday September 9, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 21)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday September 8, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 21)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday September 5, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 21)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday September 4, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 21)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday September 3, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 21)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday September 2, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 21)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday September 1, 1969. Item is in English.
- October, 1969; Publication (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 22)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday October 31, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 22)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday October 30, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 22)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday October 29, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 22)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday October 28, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 22)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday October 27, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 22)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday October 24, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 22)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday October 23, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 22)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday October 22, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 22)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday October 21, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 22)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday October 20, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 22)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday October 17, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 22)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday October 16, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 22)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday October 15, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 22)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday October 14, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 22)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday October 13, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 22)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday October 10, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 22)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday October 9, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 22)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday October 8, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 22)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday October 7, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 22)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday October 6, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 22)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday October 3, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 22)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday October 2, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 22)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday October 1, 1969. Item is in English.
- November, 1969; Publication (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 23)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday November 28, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 23)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday November 26, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 23)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday November 25, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 23)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday November 24, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 23)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday November 21, 1969. Item is in English.